fansub.tv 2008-06-24

# Fansub.TV - Privacy Policy

**What this privacy policy covers**

This policy covers how Fansub.TV treats personal information that Fansub.TV collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Fansub.TV products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Fansub.TV does not own or control, or to people that Fansub.TV does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Fansub.TV associated entities have their own privacy policies which can be viewed by clicking on their privacy policy link.

**Information Collection and Use**

  * Fansub.TV collects personal information when you register with Fansub.TV, when you use Fansub.TV products or services, when you visit Fansub.TV pages or pages of certain Fansub.TV partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Fansub.TV may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.  

  * When you register, we ask for information such as your email address, a username and password. Once you register with Fansub.TV and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.  

  * Fansub.TV collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer.  

  * Fansub.TV automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Fansub.TV cookie information, and the page you request.  

  * Fansub.TV uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Fansub.TV does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  

    * We may provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Fansub.TV under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Fansub.TV communicate with you about offers from Fansub.TV and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.  

    * We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  

    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violation of Fansub.TV's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  

    * We transfer information about you if Fansub.TV is acquired by or merged with another entity. In this event, Fansub.TV will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  

  * Fansub.TV may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.  

    * Fansub.TV does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.  

  * Fansub.TV may work with vendors, partners, advertisers, or other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

**Cookies**

  * Fansub.TV may set and access Fansub.TV cookies on your computer.  

  * Fansub.TV lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Fansub.TV's cookies.

**General**

  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Fansub.TV service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and Fansub.TV newletters, that are considered part of your Fansub.TV account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * Fansub.TV may update this policy. We may notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Fansub.TV account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
